  export const musicQuestions = [
    {
      question: "Music Who is known as the 'King of Pop'?",
      options: ["Elvis Presley", "Michael Jackson", "Madonna", "Prince"],
      correctAnswer: "Michael Jackson",
    },
    {
      question: "Music Who composed the iconic symphony 'Beethoven's 5th'?",
      options: ["Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart", "Ludwig van Beethoven", "Johann Sebastian Bach", "Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky"],
      correctAnswer: "Ludwig van Beethoven",
    },
    // {
    //   question: "Music In which decade did the Beatles first appear on 'The Ed Sullivan Show'?",
    //   options: ["1950s", "1960s", "1970s", "1980s"],
    //   correctAnswer: "1960s",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music What genre is characterized by its use of syncopated rhythms and improvisational elements?",
    //   options: ["Jazz", "Classical", "Country", "Rock"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Jazz",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Who is the lead vocalist of the rock band Queen?",
    //   options: ["Freddie Mercury", "Robert Plant", "Mick Jagger", "Axl Rose"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Freddie Mercury",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Which artist is known for hits like 'Billie Jean' and 'Thriller'?",
    //   options: ["Prince", "Madonna", "Michael Jackson", "Stevie Wonder"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Michael Jackson",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music What is the main instrument in a traditional mariachi band?",
    //   options: ["Trumpet", "Guitar", "Accordion", "Violin"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Trumpet",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Who is often referred to as the 'Queen of Soul'?",
    //   options: ["Whitney Houston", "Aretha Franklin", "Diana Ross", "Tina Turner"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Aretha Franklin",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music What legendary guitarist is known for playing with his teeth and behind his back?",
    //   options: ["Eric Clapton", "Jimi Hendrix", "Jimmy Page", "Carlos Santana"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Jimi Hendrix",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Which music streaming platform was launched by Swedish company Spotify?",
    //   options: ["Apple Music", "Tidal", "Deezer", "Spotify"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Spotify",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music In which city did the punk rock movement originate in the 1970s?",
    //   options: ["New York City", "London", "Los Angeles", "Berlin"],
    //   correctAnswer: "London",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Who is the 'Rocket Man' known for his piano-driven pop songs?",
    //   options: ["Billy Joel", "Elton John", "John Lennon", "Paul McCartney"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Elton John",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Which country is famous for the traditional music genre called 'Fado'?",
    //   options: ["Spain", "Italy", "Portugal", "Greece"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Portugal",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music What musical term refers to a gradual increase in loudness?",
    //   options: ["Crescendo", "Fortissimo", "Allegro", "Pianissimo"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Crescendo",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Who is known for pioneering the use of synthesizers in electronic music and scored 'Blade Runner'?",
    //   options: ["Jean-Michel Jarre", "Kraftwerk", "Vangelis", "Brian Eno"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Vangelis",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music What is the term for a musical composition for solo instrument or instruments?",
    //   options: ["Sonata", "Symphony", "Concerto", "Overture"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Sonata",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Who was the lead singer of the rock band Led Zeppelin?",
    //   options: ["Roger Daltrey", "Robert Plant", "Mick Jagger", "David Bowie"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Robert Plant",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music In which country did the dance music genre 'Samba' originate?",
    //   options: ["Argentina", "Brazil", "Cuba", "Mexico"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Brazil",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music What is the term for the speed at which a piece of music is played?",
    //   options: ["Tempo", "Rhythm", "Melody", "Harmony"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Tempo",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Who is known as the 'Queen of Pop'?",
    //   options: ["Madonna", "Britney Spears", "Lady Gaga", "Katy Perry"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Madonna",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Which instrument does Yo-Yo Ma play?",
    //   options: ["Violin", "Cello", "Piano", "Flute"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Cello",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Who is known for the hit song 'Bohemian Rhapsody'?",
    //   options: ["The Rolling Stones", "Queen", "The Beatles", "Led Zeppelin"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Queen",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music What is the term for a musical piece for two performers?",
    //   options: ["Duet", "Trio", "Quartet", "Solo"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Duet",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Who is the 'Material Girl' known for her iconic fashion and pop hits?",
    //   options: ["Britney Spears", "Lady Gaga", "Madonna", "Katy Perry"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Madonna",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music In which year did the legendary Woodstock music festival take place?",
    //   options: ["1967", "1969", "1971", "1973"],
    //   correctAnswer: "1969",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music What genre is characterized by its use of turntables and sampling?",
    //   options: ["Rock", "Hip Hop", "Country", "Reggae"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Hip Hop",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Who is the lead singer of the rock band U2?",
    //   options: ["Bono", "Chris Martin", "Dave Grohl", "Eddie Vedder"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Bono",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Which music legend is known for 'Your Song'?",
    //   options: ["Elton John", "Billy Joel", "Stevie Wonder", "John Lennon"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Elton John",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music What is the term for a gradual decrease in loudness in a piece of music?",
    //   options: ["Decrescendo", "Pianissimo", "Fortissimo", "Crescendo"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Decrescendo",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Who is the 'Purple Haze' guitarist famous for his blues-inspired rock music?",
    //   options: ["Eric Clapton", "Jimmy Page", "Jimi Hendrix", "Carlos Santana"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Jimi Hendrix",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music What is the main ingredient in traditional Japanese Taiko drumming?",
    //   options: ["Wood", "Metal", "Leather", "Skin"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Skin",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music Who is known for the classic hit 'Like a Rolling Stone'?",
    //   options: ["Bob Marley", "Bob Dylan", "Bruce Springsteen", "Tom Petty"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Bob Dylan",
    // },
    // {
    //   question: "Music What Latin dance originated in the 1920s and became a popular music genre?",
    //   options: ["Salsa", "Tango", "Merengue", "Samba"],
    //   correctAnswer: "Samba",
    // },
];
